Heh.
Pretty good!
00:01:04,040 -  -> 00:01:04,400
Of
Pretty good!
Of Course!
You've come so far my children
But you'll know I'll take you further
Just shake my hand and you'll truly be
Rid of all your burdens!
I know that deep inside yourself
You want this month to last.
So
So rid
So rid your
So rid your souls
I'll
I'll take
I'll take con
I'll take control
I'll
I'll make
I'll make the
I'll make the hor
I'll make the horror
OH
OH SO
OH SO REAL
DON'T
DON'T YOU
DON'T YOU WANT
DON'T YOU WANT THIS
TO
TO BE
TO BE REAL?
Feel yourself succumbing
There's no use in running
Time is swiftly ticking
Feel
Feel the
Warmth of your heart sinking...
As
As your
As your ov
As your over
As your overwhelmed
As you're overwhelmed with